[
  {
    "id": "01GEFPBGRC6PKNCKQTBFD8NG3X",
    "question": "What is the best dish Forsen can cook? ",
    "answer": "Steaks",
    "hint1": "No salt ",
    "hint2": "forsenE ü•©",
    "submitter": "H",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:49:49.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPBGRVHPX048X0AWQERHF7",
    "question": "In December 2021, Forsen promoted this type of product from MADMONQ",
    "answer": "Qandle",
    "hint1": "forsenInsane üïØ ",
    "hint2": "_andle",
    "submitter": "H",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:49:49.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPBHFED0BMBTZGBS6W26RK",
    "question": "What was the name of Forsen's character in Elden Ring? ",
    "answer": "Dog Tamer ",
    "hint1": "forsenSmug SmugTime ",
    "hint2": "D__ Ta___",
    "submitter": "H",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:49:50.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPBJ4JX8XG51Q1065FMV0Z",
    "question": "When browsing through forsen's unofficial Subreddit in 2022, you'll mostly likely see one of the 'daily posts' featuring this emote",
    "answer": "forsenLevel",
    "hint1": "Rage comics ",
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "zileaon1",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:49:51.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPBKBY65Y5NNQH5F5VKX5N",
    "question": "In a 2014 twitch party, forsen grabbed this streamer's butt after she made a portrait of him.",
    "answer": "MissCoookiez",
    "hint1": "M___C___k___",
    "hint2": "Mi__Co__ki__",
    "submitter": "iNF3CT0Rz",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:49:52.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPBKEVJPVC0ZWJF5ZWES6A",
    "question": "How many times did forsen die in Eldest Souls?",
    "answer": "139",
    "hint1": null,
    "hint2": "Less than 200",
    "submitter": "zileaon1",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:49:52.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPBKF5SGWWJTK33KH8FMX9",
    "question": "How many hours did forsen take to complete Jump King: Ghost of the Babe? (Bog DLC)",
    "answer": "56 Hours",
    "hint1": "__ Hours",
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "Cenrus",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:49:52.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPBKFEEA94ZZ36RCTWRWVQ",
    "question": "What is Forsens profile picture on steam?",
    "answer": "forsenWut",
    "hint1": "It is one of his subscriber emotes",
    "hint2": "uhhhhhhhhhh",
    "submitter": "Cenrus",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:49:52.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPBKQZ1GH0R3RWWVBV6NGA",
    "question": "You got permanently banned from the channel, what do you do?",
    "answer": "Donate and ask for an unban",
    "hint1": "Forsen is actually very forgiving, im sure he would consider giving you a second chance",
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "idksomeguy",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:49:53.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPBKRCXWM3HW255QQEMPC9",
    "question": "how big is forsens ego?",
    "answer": "unquantifiable",
    "hint1": null,
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "idksomeguy",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:49:53.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPBKTKTEZJYDHV4VVYTAV4",
    "question": "Forsen is taking the day off, what do you do?",
    "answer": "Do something else 4Head",
    "hint1": "4Head",
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "idksomeguy",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:49:53.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPBKW49SB742YYV8PKQ5QH",
    "question": "This happens when you type !",
    "answer": "Snusbot also types !",
    "hint1": null,
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "idksomeguy",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:49:53.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPBKWG8Y9TBJYJ9VZMHDT0",
    "question": "People forsen has locked up in his basement",
    "answer": "real forsen and nina (skeletal remains) ",
    "hint1": null,
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "idksomeguy",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:49:53.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPBKY0GM5RVHQ0DN66E93A",
    "question": "Forsen is bleeding out",
    "answer": "OH GOD LULW FUCK LULW GOD LULW FUCK LULW GOTTA STOP THE BLEEDING LULW",
    "hint1": null,
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "idksomeguy",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:49:53.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPBKYKDNCD7B19ZQW87STQ",
    "question": "forsen",
    "answer": "forsen",
    "hint1": "forsen",
    "hint2": "forsen",
    "submitter": "idksomeguy",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:49:53.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPBM0E0X2YPW1P88XDMAGM",
    "question": "forsen just leveled in an autobattler",
    "answer": "forsenBased",
    "hint1": "HOLY",
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "idksomeguy",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:49:53.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPBMAQAX380T5YKSRPPHAS",
    "question": "Approach with caution! No __________ or allowed.",
    "answer": "roleplaying & tryharding",
    "hint1": "forsenRP & TriHard ",
    "hint2": "ro__p__y___ & tr_ha____g",
    "submitter": null,
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:49:53.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPBMB3TKYPQR3WARPGTGE2",
    "question": "What was Forsen's death count in Garlic?",
    "answer": "2691",
    "hint1": "26__",
    "hint2": "269_",
    "submitter": "Kazahaner",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:49:53.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPBMBEKA9ZX3V6S23T9AYJ",
    "question": "You have you risk it ___ ___ _______ Pepepains",
    "answer": "for the biscuit",
    "hint1": "cookie :)",
    "hint2": "for the b______",
    "submitter": null,
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:49:53.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPBMCJT83WGF26MFENRAHY",
    "question": "You just won the raffle, what should you do now? :tf:",
    "answer": "Give it to someone else",
    "hint1": "Give __ __ _______ ____ :tf:",
    "hint2": "Give it to _______ ____ :tf:",
    "submitter": null,
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:49:53.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPBMGZEG1HZ40DX5R2J0KS",
    "question": "How many non-weeb mods are in Forsen's channel?",
    "answer": "0  ",
    "hint1": "Not many :/",
    "hint2": "_",
    "submitter": null,
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:49:53.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPBMJ34YF06MD6MWGDK5Y3",
    "question": "Forsen's alternative account ",
    "answer": "Gawr Gura",
    "hint1": "NaM",
    "hint2": "Ga__ Gu__",
    "submitter": null,
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:49:53.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPBN4XBK87FN8VEX4E7PEE",
    "question": "Best Forsen line?",
    "answer": "Previously on Lost",
    "hint1": "forsenGa where am I chat",
    "hint2": "Pre_______ __ ____",
    "submitter": "Kazahaner",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:49:54.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPBNCPSTGQTPHQQ5QZ57Z1",
    "question": "What was Forsen's time on his first completed Minecraft speedrun? forsenInsane",
    "answer": "1:02:10",
    "hint1": "Slightly over an hour :)",
    "hint2": "1:02:__",
    "submitter": "Kazahaner",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:49:54.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPBNN58RCP44ABFAG15HRD",
    "question": "a common command that people use in offline chat forsenScoots",
    "answer": "+ed",
    "hint1": " hackerCD ",
    "hint2": "VaN",
    "submitter": "j0yeg",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:49:54.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPBNPJR03JNJK1514QAKJ2",
    "question": "is nina alive?",
    "answer": "Copesen yes",
    "hint1": null,
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "j0yeg",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:49:55.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPBNTKMQEXHF3C02GS7Q19",
    "question": "What is the only Dark Souls boss Forsen never defeated?",
    "answer": "Lud & Zallen",
    "hint1": "He killed Midir during his DS3 Cinders playthrough",
    "hint2": "Boss area is outside of Frozen Eleum Loyce",
    "submitter": null,
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:49:55.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPBNTX0NWNW7QENYF3B07J",
    "question": "Forsen most likely will never play this game",
    "answer": "Hollow Knight",
    "hint1": "It gets suggested every time for a new playthrough",
    "hint2": "Copesen someday...",
    "submitter": null,
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:49:55.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPBPNXF1E3BFWZDH5DRN9K",
    "question": "What day did Forsen first play Minecraft?",
    "answer": "May 23, 2020",
    "hint1": "forsenInsane",
    "hint2": "May __ _0_0",
    "submitter": null,
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:49:56.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPBPYFW8C6G25TJDWHB7EY",
    "question": "How many deaths did forsen have in his Struggling playthrough?",
    "answer": "187 deaths",
    "hint1": "three digits + \"deaths\"",
    "hint2": "1 _ _ deaths",
    "submitter": "carbon monoxide poisoning victim",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:49:56.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPBR4VMAHY4EWJ0ZPHZ45Y",
    "question": "What was the first character forsen plays as in Tekken 7?",
    "answer": "Yoshimitsu",
    "hint1": null,
    "hint2": "Harakiri",
    "submitter": "fablearctic",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:49:57.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPBRXTJW2PZFHP939A2CSF",
    "question": "How many times did forsen die during his Titan Souls playthrough?",
    "answer": "208",
    "hint1": null,
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "me :)",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:49:58.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPBSD26Y5J03KR0ZPTM2PN",
    "question": "How is somebody homeless?",
    "answer": "Just get a house",
    "hint1": "4House",
    "hint2": "4House",
    "submitter": "ur mom lol",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:49:58.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPBSET1BJK0QAPSHR3W2NW",
    "question": "In the fanfic 'Eolnyss', these powerful individuals received teachings from and protected dragons",
    "answer": "Dragon knights",
    "hint1": null,
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "ur mom lol",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:49:58.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPBSHT63WH7D8K3K5E9FC8",
    "question": "What is this, damage for... ? forsenE ",
    "answer": "ants",
    "hint1": null,
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "atgazatufeelsdankman",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:49:58.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPBSRBMBV9DGNGDSEK3GS5",
    "question": "Guess who will win this trivia again?",
    "answer": "Cspice",
    "hint1": null,
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "ZeZerT",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:49:59.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPBSVAV4N71Q1J7BPRZZZ2",
    "question": "In a poll in 2019 it was said that 87 percent of Forsen bajs are also viewers of?",
    "answer": "Xqcow",
    "hint1": null,
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "GolanTrev",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:49:59.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPBSXDRM9AN5WXG5CYD13R",
    "question": "Forsen played these two games in his first ever stream?",
    "answer": "Starcraft and Left for Dead",
    "hint1": null,
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": null,
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:49:59.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPBSYJ2RYHRJ1D4R5Y6CN0",
    "question": "What did Forsen specialise in during his Skyrim playthrough?",
    "answer": "Archery",
    "hint1": null,
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "ur mom lol",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:49:59.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPBT3N10BZNRHMMZPDP0F3",
    "question": "forsen1 forsen2",
    "answer": "forsen3 forsen4",
    "hint1": null,
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": null,
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:49:59.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPBTA63TKZZPK9SR2NWS65",
    "question": "forsenT admin how to __________",
    "answer": "delet my account",
    "hint1": "forsenWut",
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "ur mom lol",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:49:59.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPBTHY278RYDHBRN4NGFDW",
    "question": "What was the chance of getting paired with üç´  or üçû 4/5 times in the tournament?",
    "answer": "0.24%",
    "hint1": null,
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "ur mom lol",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:00.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPBTRVAFPJ25CZ9VWGDFQQ",
    "question": "In Forsen's fanfic 'Eolnyss', what magical art does Damien specialise in?",
    "answer": "Deamon arts",
    "hint1": null,
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "ur mom lol",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:00.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPBTZ14F6NANFCQ9K9MPJG",
    "question": "so bald",
    "answer": "so mald",
    "hint1": "pepeLaugh",
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "rosethemagician",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:00.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPBV2JEESESP4B0H55ZZMD",
    "question": "What is the name of the fanfic written by forsen1337 in 2007?",
    "answer": "Eolnyss",
    "hint1": null,
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "ur mom lol",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:00.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPBVAGJ67Q5NRQXESN8MWY",
    "question": "During a exclusive streamer dinner at Twitchcon in 2015, there was a credit card roulette game. Who won?",
    "answer": "LegendaryLea",
    "hint1": "Famous Leech",
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "Noobberry",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:00.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPBVBJJE4ZWFKK375SM8HN",
    "question": "Article 13 was passed when?",
    "answer": "April 1st",
    "hint1": null,
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "Cyclik[",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:00.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPBVDYY0BSGTBC8DSDEFJ7",
    "question": "What emote has been removed/re-added the most?",
    "answer": "forsenClown",
    "hint1": "forsen________",
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "atgazatufeelsdankman",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:00.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPBVJN1VKPB1ED14KHZ93V",
    "question": "How long is Forsen's D gachiBASS",
    "answer": "5cm long",
    "hint1": null,
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": null,
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:01.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPBVS3JXATY3PTEF2HZA09",
    "question": "Who made The Snus Brotherhood?",
    "answer": "Bobosse",
    "hint1": null,
    "hint2": "B________",
    "submitter": "atgazatufeelsdankman",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:01.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPBVZJHPYDT5WBQB4Q0546",
    "question": "What games did Forsen play on his 1 year anniversary?",
    "answer": "Starcraft, Portal and League",
    "hint1": null,
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "YABU",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:01.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPBWCYE04A61P1K50R1RY7",
    "question": "Forsen picked this card instead of another sinister strike.",
    "answer": "Deadly poison",
    "hint1": "18/30 cards",
    "hint2": "Dea___ p_____",
    "submitter": "Tajmon00rvnge",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:01.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPBWFTNHPAFV8N1JNWXCFK",
    "question": "Which legendary sword did Forsen sell in Skyrim?",
    "answer": "Chillrend",
    "hint1": ":snowflake: :dagger:",
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "ur mom lol",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:01.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPBXBGC43D7HG5ZCZK6EG6",
    "question": "What is forsens pet? ",
    "answer": "üêÄ",
    "hint1": "forsSmash ",
    "hint2": "forsSmash  Peppah",
    "submitter": "Dollt28",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:02.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPBXM9BYG9NCD97ZBECS50",
    "question": "PUBG",
    "answer": "OMEGALUL",
    "hint1": null,
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "TormentDubz",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:03.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPBXWYTY1WN2QP09BSBDVR",
    "question": "During his Hearthstone times he was also known as the prince of",
    "answer": "miracoli",
    "hint1": null,
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "UNLOLS",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:03.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPBYKXS10SPS6NHYQE7KJT",
    "question": "How long did it take forsen to beat Sonic in I Wanna Be The Boshy?",
    "answer": "7 days",
    "hint1": "A lot of time ",
    "hint2": "777 forsenPls 777 forsenPls 777 forsenPls",
    "submitter": "NaM NaM NaM",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:04.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPBYMVXGHB1FYNV00RC9DR",
    "question": "Who is the most annoying trivia farmer in offline chat?",
    "answer": "Marcedone",
    "hint1": "He only farms 1 category forsenSleeper",
    "hint2": "Mar_____",
    "submitter": "Marcedone",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:04.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPBYVXNFYJPA6QR2GW3F0Z",
    "question": "How many Swedish streamers exist?",
    "answer": "2",
    "hint1": null,
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "YABU",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:04.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPBYZBKQ6E0RF4H7STRZCX",
    "question": "Who carried Forsen through the Skyrim playthrough?",
    "answer": "Lydia",
    "hint1": "L____",
    "hint2": "Lyd__",
    "submitter": "Dollt28",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:04.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPBZ8B97QWXVRCE06B5CS0",
    "question": "forsenOG Where's my ... ?",
    "answer": "auctioneer",
    "hint1": "a_________",
    "hint2": "auc_______",
    "submitter": "Tajmon00rvnge",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:04.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPBZC1K2W7VDCXW0R6TP3N",
    "question": "If you Snus?",
    "answer": "You loose",
    "hint1": "You...",
    "hint2": "Lose",
    "submitter": "EpicMango7",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:04.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPC01HAHQNVP0EYMN940S8",
    "question": "Forsen died in Radical Heights by taking out this instead of a gun forsenSWA",
    "answer": "a medkit",
    "hint1": "PepeLaugh :point_right: forsenSWA :heavy_plus_sign:",
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "ur mom lol",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:05.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPC05AS2PFY6944FE6TKHX",
    "question": "Which sub is the most racist?",
    "answer": "Forsen subs aren‚Äôt racist :)",
    "hint1": null,
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "Cyclik[",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:05.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPC05Z3TBRAGQ2N1HBWPKQ",
    "question": "When browsing through forsen's unofficial Subreddit, you'll mostly likely see one of the 'daily posts' depicting a picture of this",
    "answer": "Solgryn",
    "hint1": "_______ It's \"unofficial\" because the mod there refused to add other moderators a few years back forsenScoots ",
    "hint2": "ItsBoshyTime ",
    "submitter": "atgazatufeelsdankman",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:05.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPC13TDNZ7JR5EFVJGC6V6",
    "question": "What is the capital of Eolnyss in Forsen's fanfic?",
    "answer": "Treno",
    "hint1": null,
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "ur mom lol",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:06.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPC1HEAQTZNGSCAG45941B",
    "question": "What does Xqcow stand for?",
    "answer": "Xtreme Queen Conner Overwatch",
    "hint1": null,
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "GolanTrev",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:07.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPC1N03SX0ZCW767FPTQ6Z",
    "question": "I CANT C",
    "answer": "forsenT",
    "hint1": null,
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": null,
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:07.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPC237TBQ104R7ESXF9YQC",
    "question": "Forsen said he would probably retire from streaming at what age?",
    "answer": "30",
    "hint1": null,
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "Cyclik[",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:07.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPC2AY6M43GTD85YP03JVA",
    "question": "Who was voted the most popular mod ",
    "answer": "Ampzyh",
    "hint1": null,
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "owo",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:07.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPC2B7K6SG05YVTAT70FK5",
    "question": "What is Forsen‚Äôs favorite movie?",
    "answer": "Inception",
    "hint1": null,
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "YABU",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:07.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPC2T6ZNHFK7RN9GGESJTY",
    "question": "What was forsen's final score in his miracle rogue arena run?",
    "answer": "1-3",
    "hint1": "LULW",
    "hint2": "1__",
    "submitter": "Tajmon00rvnge",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:08.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPC3ETJ17H0Q3BB63Q9VDP",
    "question": "Which famous youtuber played with Forsen in Pubg?",
    "answer": "Pewdiepie ",
    "hint1": "Swedish",
    "hint2": "European",
    "submitter": "I‚Äôm l",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:09.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPC3RAAF1XZ7848V5CDYST",
    "question": "I just want to suck his...",
    "answer": "swedish meatballs",
    "hint1": "Kappa",
    "hint2": "sw_____ _________",
    "submitter": "Tajmon00rvnge",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:09.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPC3ZE6M13BJAF1ZJ7P17S",
    "question": "Gazatu said he would look into removing all the retarded questions, but didn't",
    "answer": "True",
    "hint1": null,
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": null,
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:09.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPC55Z5DNQAHNAYP8DQXCY",
    "question": "Oh really?",
    "answer": "forsenScoots",
    "hint1": "Interesting",
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "atgazatufeelsdankman",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:10.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPC575MYVR92NASWQHVCM8",
    "question": "FITTA",
    "answer": "forsenSWA",
    "hint1": null,
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": null,
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:10.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPC58XJ7SRTNS93K7BDQ1J",
    "question": "What Luck stat did Forsen have in Fallout New Vegas?",
    "answer": "10",
    "hint1": null,
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "xXx420MLGMaster_uw0tm8xXx",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:10.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPC59N2E1V2SRJEHFCQZ15",
    "question": "What was xqc‚Äôs name on GTA RP",
    "answer": "JEan pierre",
    "hint1": null,
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "GolanTrev",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:10.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPC5KRYET8SSM1AV04Q1EK",
    "question": "Old age?",
    "answer": "The Time Wizard",
    "hint1": "gachiHYPER",
    "hint2": "jump off the bridge",
    "submitter": "SELLOUTSEN",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:11.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPC5RV4K59NKTSN430F28M",
    "question": "Where's my ______ bro?",
    "answer": "Leeroy",
    "hint1": "L_____",
    "hint2": "Lee___",
    "submitter": "Tajmon00rvnge",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:11.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPC5WKECAH9KB0PNPZ9CVY",
    "question": "In Forsen's fanfic 'Eolnyss', What move does Damien use to defeat Gill?",
    "answer": "Deamon arts: Dark matter",
    "hint1": ":black_circle: ‚úã forsen1337",
    "hint2": "Deamon arts: ___________",
    "submitter": "ur mom lol",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:11.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPC61QE1RJXRXT9EHFJ8SJ",
    "question": "Use this command to fist gazatu2",
    "answer": "!$fist gazatu2",
    "hint1": "gachiGASM -$300",
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "atgazatufeelsdankman",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:11.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPC66HS4ADVKZ3JVPYKDHX",
    "question": "Type !commands to win this round",
    "answer": "Snusbot commands available here: forsen.tv/commands",
    "hint1": "!comman__",
    "hint2": "!command_",
    "submitter": "FawcanTV",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:11.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPC6D87A58HC7CGAQ4AJZZ",
    "question": "How much?",
    "answer": "Yes 100",
    "hint1": null,
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "Cyclik[",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:12.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPC73C9J1F3E0AZ55K4K6E",
    "question": "How old was Forsen when Nani baked him a birthday pancake?",
    "answer": "28",
    "hint1": null,
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "Noobberry",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:12.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPC79RT55WYRVH177K1Q49",
    "question": "Emote combo: Hold your horses! forsenE",
    "answer": "monkaS / üê¥",
    "hint1": "m_____ / :_____:",
    "hint2": "m____S / :h___e:",
    "submitter": "atgazatufeelsdankman",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:13.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPC7FGETKTJ56BFQSFVP32",
    "question": "Name three of Forsen‚Äôs ex girlfriends?",
    "answer": "Nani, Tigerbarr and Eloise",
    "hint1": "Women",
    "hint2": "Streamers",
    "submitter": "EpicMango7",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:13.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPC7TFSJBCBT9PDCMVMX11",
    "question": "In Forsen's chat on 27 Dec 2019, what did wuzkangznshiet say in response to TriHard spam?",
    "answer": "DETROIT CHAT WutFace",
    "hint1": null,
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "TormentDubz",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:13.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPC8A3HY2ZRH9NKV34D0C0",
    "question": "In Forsen's fanfic 'Eolnyss', Vincent's armour is made of this, considered one of the strongest materials in Eolnyss.",
    "answer": "Dragon scale",
    "hint1": null,
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "ur mom lol",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:14.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPC8A948SYPCYBF424X1CC",
    "question": "There are 3 exclusive Cumwatch shifts, Noobberry and Forsen owns one but who is the 3rd?",
    "answer": "DeerNadia",
    "hint1": "Female streamer",
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "Noobberry",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:14.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPC8EYNZPDDYNT3P0E7T41",
    "question": "Who killed Lydia in Forsen's playthrough of Skyrim?",
    "answer": "Forsen",
    "hint1": "LYDIA PepeHands",
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "ur mom lol",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:14.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPC8N7S9HC9VX9743DKPP1",
    "question": "What message was donated to Forsen during his Skyrim debut that eventually became a Forsen emote?",
    "answer": "You have chicken legs Forsen lol",
    "hint1": "You have...",
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "deatron",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:14.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPC8VQBMS2BE5D9EVW0D0V",
    "question": "In Forsen's fanfic 'Eolnyss', How old is Molly?",
    "answer": "21",
    "hint1": "number spam FeelsGoodMan Clap",
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "ur mom lol",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:14.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPC8Z606S9VB41ADXF22X0",
    "question": "Which game did Forsen play based off Cube movies?",
    "answer": "HaIf Dead 2",
    "hint1": null,
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "Cyclik[",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:14.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPC99TE35S98GZ48E92Z0Z",
    "question": "How many shadowsteps did forsen have in his miracle rogue run?",
    "answer": "three",
    "hint1": "GabeN",
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "Tajmon00rvnge",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:15.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPC9NS6BHE02ZH8Z13MDNG",
    "question": "What is Forsen's death count in the Legend of Selda, Breath of the Wild? forsenT",
    "answer": "135",
    "hint1": "check sne forsenE",
    "hint2": "number spam FeelsGoodMan Clap",
    "submitter": "ur mom lol",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:15.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPCAA3Q54TB8XFK0EZXSM6",
    "question": "Okayge TeaTime _ _ _ _ :question:",
    "answer": "COCK",
    "hint1": "Okayge TeaTime",
    "hint2": "Okayge TeaTime",
    "submitter": "delta__forsen",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:16.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPCACCTBPG6ESMM0GZRAF3",
    "question": "What did forsen get for his 20th card pick?",
    "answer": "Gadgetzan Auctioneer",
    "hint1": "PogChamp OH MY GOD",
    "hint2": "gad______ a__________",
    "submitter": "Tajmon00rvnge",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:16.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPCAG286VN54X4D0KRRRD1",
    "question": "What's the initial velocity of a moving object?",
    "answer": "V1 ZULUL",
    "hint1": null,
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": null,
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:16.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPCARYEZGDT7DJXR9HW1X9",
    "question": "According to forsen, you should to this instead of voting.",
    "answer": "Work at McDonalds",
    "hint1": "forsenGa",
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "Forsen",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:16.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPCAXHZCBF5PG55KXV3E5G",
    "question": "I NEED ... FOR MIRACLE ROGUE forsenOG",
    "answer": "Coldlight Oracle",
    "hint1": "1/30 cards",
    "hint2": "Col______ ______",
    "submitter": "Tajmon00rvnge",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:16.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPCAY8SNWW032FH3KDWXHV",
    "question": "In Forsen's fanfic 'Eolnyss', What ability does Vincent use to scout for enemies?",
    "answer": "Dragon vision",
    "hint1": ":dragon: forsen1",
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "ur mom lol",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:16.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPCB349RNBPP841MK8DHW4",
    "question": "RELAX",
    "answer": "forsenW",
    "hint1": null,
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": null,
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:16.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPCB3CYJVB49A2VBA5DF9W",
    "question": "What is Forsen‚Äôs favorite color?",
    "answer": "Read",
    "hint1": null,
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "YABU",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:16.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPCBHKD4TG1KH78K5K97S9",
    "question": "DO THIS BEFORE VOTING. :rage:",
    "answer": "READ ALL THREE CHAPTERS",
    "hint1": "NARUTOSEN OMEGALUL",
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "ur mom lol",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:17.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPCBKDR97J0Q3E0VS4557K",
    "question": "who is the most loved brazilian baj ?",
    "answer": "rosethemagician",
    "hint1": "pink name",
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "rosethemagician",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:17.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPCBRYHS3RCR0X8E1CZDCY",
    "question": "Which is the most hated mod?",
    "answer": "How dare you insult a mod",
    "hint1": null,
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "owo",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:17.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPCBWHBKAP0K5EE39FE0HS",
    "question": "In Forsen's fanfic 'Eolnyss', what weapon does Bill use?",
    "answer": "a giant hammer",
    "hint1": ":hammer: KKonaW",
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "ur mom lol",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:17.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPCBX4VMXXGYSMC4EBR543",
    "question": "In Mysterious Girlfriend X, what object does Mikoto Urabe tuck in her panties?",
    "answer": "Scissors",
    "hint1": "Sc______",
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "Noobberry",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:17.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPCC42PEPX01K9GA7KP7H4",
    "question": "Which emote is ACTUALLY Forsen's best emote?",
    "answer": "forsenE",
    "hint1": null,
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "TormentDubz",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:17.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPCC4ARD7H7S2HQ4ST036N",
    "question": "What is the name of the world in which Forsen's fanfic, written in 2007, is set?",
    "answer": "Eolnyss",
    "hint1": null,
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "ur mom lol",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:17.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPCC9MSHWA3MA4XZ9604MX",
    "question": "What is forsen's favorite Snus?",
    "answer": "General G3",
    "hint1": null,
    "hint2": "G_______ ___ - Don't do drugs kids :)",
    "submitter": "atgazatufeelsdankman",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:18.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPCCNQ2BWTCVE9BS1VQ4AJ",
    "question": "What is Forsen‚Äôs favorite tv show?",
    "answer": "The Sopranos",
    "hint1": null,
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "YABU",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:18.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPCCS75YNPSEMREVVDEAVD",
    "question": "Which emote was added in May of 2019?",
    "answer": "forsenChickenlegs",
    "hint1": "forsenC...",
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "I‚Äôm l",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:18.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPCD9Z7DXVSDTRJZPWD4Y0",
    "question": "Name all four of Forsen‚Äôs girlfriends?",
    "answer": "Nina, Eloise, Tyggbarr and Bethany ",
    "hint1": "Nin...",
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "I‚Äôm l",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:19.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPCDC73GTNK7VENK8RDN5M",
    "question": "Who is the editor in forsen's Youtube channel?",
    "answer": "Holeekebab",
    "hint1": null,
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "atgazatufeelsdankman",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:19.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPCDV0FNBB6N55MA30X2RM",
    "question": "Which Forsen sub called Bajs stupid, immature and racist in 2017?",
    "answer": "Blowmymnd",
    "hint1": "Blo",
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "muricanslol",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:19.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPCDVM4FW6ZAA36CAFGD18",
    "question": "uhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh",
    "answer": "forsenWut",
    "hint1": null,
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "randers00",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:19.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPCDZP3WNY727BPKGQDNSY",
    "question": "What is Forsen's death count in the Adventures of pepeL ?",
    "answer": "399",
    "hint1": "not a smol number pepeL",
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "chiaryan",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:19.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPCE5K06Y00SV5XSKY634P",
    "question": "What spice does Forsen hate?",
    "answer": "Cinnamon",
    "hint1": null,
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "Noobberry",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:20.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPCE6GV86WE8EJR296J1W7",
    "question": "whats gazatus favorite emote ?",
    "answer": "FeelsDankMan",
    "hint1": null,
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "rosethemagician",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:20.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPCEBVWTFQPZK5NZ6NYMAF",
    "question": "First words of the day",
    "answer": "Good fucking morning bajs",
    "hint1": "22 letters, 3 spaces",
    "hint2": "Good fucking _______ ____",
    "submitter": "DustyMcBacon",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:20.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPCES63VY33M6NBE87FG4N",
    "question": "OH MY GOD!!!! _ ____ ___ __ __________ !",
    "answer": "I just got an auctioneer",
    "hint1": "PogChamp",
    "hint2": "I just g__ __ __________ ",
    "submitter": "Tajmon00rvnge",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:20.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPCESHWVVRRYTEMTF142ZQ",
    "question": "Which Subnautica monster led to forsenWTF ?",
    "answer": "Reaper Leviathan",
    "hint1": "Reaper _________",
    "hint2": "Reaper Levi_____",
    "submitter": "ur mom lol",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:20.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPCEZGJ8SXT54MZZAW5ZZW",
    "question": "Forsen played as this race in Skyrim",
    "answer": "Khajiit",
    "hint1": "This race is talented in stealth",
    "hint2": "CoolCat Clap",
    "submitter": "ur mom lol",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:20.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPCF5D39125M70AH6S6ARC",
    "question": "who was the first editor of the fun facts in saturday night e?",
    "answer": "DFantasy",
    "hint1": null,
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": null,
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:21.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPCFBFM2JH1RWTKDFSK6EQ",
    "question": "Shaman, priest or rogue?",
    "answer": "Oh yeah I'm gonna be the miracle rogue here ",
    "hint1": "O_ y___ I__ g____ b_ ___ m______ _____ h___",
    "hint2": "Oh yeah I'm gonna be ___ m______ r____ h____",
    "submitter": "Tajmon00rvnge",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:21.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPCFK8WZ2D397SR9XD2BQP",
    "question": "What was the first ever Forsen emote?",
    "answer": "forsenTwitch",
    "hint1": "forsen...",
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "sinris ",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:21.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPCG6416CYHEJNCVZ349HH",
    "question": "Who made 'I wanna be the forsenbaj'?",
    "answer": "fatherpucci1",
    "hint1": null,
    "hint2": "f____________1",
    "submitter": "atgazatufeelsdankman",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:22.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPCG89QDD6FFVD2H7Z32Q3",
    "question": "What was forsens 14th ever emote?",
    "answer": "forsenClown",
    "hint1": null,
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "YABU",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:22.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPCGB3HXNC2J8QGY17FRXR",
    "question": "In Forsen's fanfic 'Eolnyss', what magical art does Vincent specialise in?",
    "answer": "Dragon arts",
    "hint1": null,
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "ur mom lol",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:22.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPCGBR9AS2QTPJ2QB7BQDK",
    "question": "What forsen meme is associated with spamming song lyrics in chat forsenPls",
    "answer": "Brainpower",
    "hint1": null,
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "Snailcat ",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:22.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPCH1GJ75AGZ5952CE7459",
    "question": "How long did it take Forsen to defeat Fume Knight in Dark Souls 2?",
    "answer": "Three hours",
    "hint1": null,
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "ur mom lol",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:23.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPCHM3NSZCTPFGC2AV7GGW",
    "question": "What did forsen name himself in Adventures of pepeL?",
    "answer": "pepeL",
    "hint1": null,
    "hint2": "p______",
    "submitter": "atgazatufeelsdankman",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:23.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPCHPCWYTAPH94YAWWNTPT",
    "question": "When will Nani get pregnant?",
    "answer": "soon",
    "hint1": "The answer has 4 characters",
    "hint2": "So__",
    "submitter": "MeguruMegu",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:23.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPCJ10VAHFRXPQE8W7YX1A",
    "question": "How many times did forsen die in zelda: breath of the wild ?",
    "answer": "135",
    "hint1": "1__",
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "rosethemagician",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:24.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPCJD7VVTX9HCKGHXDYE2W",
    "question": "What is the best command in Forsen's chat?",
    "answer": "!enation",
    "hint1": null,
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "TormentDubz",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:24.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPCJHN1TWJFEZNPYSN0CDM",
    "question": "WE ARE READY FOR MY SUMMER",
    "answer": "CAR FeelsGoodMan",
    "hint1": null,
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "TormentDubz",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:24.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPCJJPEAE4NMCAHW2N6RGV",
    "question": "What is the forsen build in CS:GO?",
    "answer": "Awp and a decoy",
    "hint1": "$4800",
    "hint2": "Decoysen MegaLUL",
    "submitter": "Dankardo",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:24.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPCJX6A72W7PE5TY7TE240",
    "question": "Under what game title is Forsen featured in Cloud9's website as a \"Pro-Player\"?",
    "answer": "Fortnite",
    "hint1": "Jebaited",
    "hint2": "F________",
    "submitter": "atgazatufeelsdankman",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:24.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPCM83NX6J6RJ7SQF9NPFD",
    "question": "How many followers does Forsen have?",
    "answer": "Approximately at this time of writing over one million ",
    "hint1": "One",
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "Mikkusha",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:26.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPCMDR50PH4H1AQFED7H4A",
    "question": "How many girlfriends has Forsen had?",
    "answer": "Four",
    "hint1": null,
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "sinris ",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:26.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPCMHN8RXPYRWA7XM1EGWQ",
    "question": "IN SVIDEN...",
    "answer": "forsenGa",
    "hint1": null,
    "hint2": "ùìòùìù ùì¢ùì•ùìîùììùìîùìù",
    "submitter": "atgazatufeelsdankman",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:26.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPCMP98XF0RXV8W4MFGF45",
    "question": "Which emote was added in March of 2019?",
    "answer": "forsenStock",
    "hint1": "Emote",
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "sinris ",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:26.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPCMW7PSSF4PGY9P99Q70G",
    "question": "there we go master... forsenE",
    "answer": "Bruce",
    "hint1": null,
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "atgazatufeelsdankman",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:26.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPCNBVXZHR9PX0GGMPB7TR",
    "question": "PLUG-DJ FORSEN forsenPls",
    "answer": "Bring me a cancer",
    "hint1": null,
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "atgazatufeelsdankman",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:27.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPCNQXQB0X1VCMS3X1DG92",
    "question": "Which good looking Forsen sub managed to get his hands on a rare Death Stranding collector‚Äôs edition? (only 1000 are available in the world)",
    "answer": "Travicity",
    "hint1": "Red name and sexy",
    "hint2": "Tr",
    "submitter": "Travicity",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:27.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPCNTJ5R5EZ15EDGY934ZW",
    "question": "In Sviiden",
    "answer": "Sven Snusberg",
    "hint1": ":tophat: forsenGa ",
    "hint2": "forsenGa I'm Sven",
    "submitter": "Bruce U",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:27.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPCNVHA0WPDHF8KAHD15AF",
    "question": "Move cam? where do you want it? forsenE ",
    "answer": "Middle center PogChamp",
    "hint1": "PogChamp",
    "hint2": "Mi____ c_____ Po_C____",
    "submitter": "atgazatufeelsdankman",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:27.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPCNVVZVCF9EKC5BS9JBEK",
    "question": "This great emote should be hanged next to the Mona Lisa.",
    "answer": "forsenD",
    "hint1": null,
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "Noobberry",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:27.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPCPASMTAPMV1ENEJNCYRW",
    "question": "Who donated over 5k to Forsen in March?",
    "answer": "Flugo",
    "hint1": "F",
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "deatron",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:28.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPCPEA924S8856VX4YQTJR",
    "question": "\"That sounds retarded\" \" It sounds like Forsen is having an orgasm on stream\"",
    "answer": "SHIV",
    "hint1": "14/30 cards",
    "hint2": "sh__",
    "submitter": "Tajmon00rvnge",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:28.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPCPEKHC0YWJ8TQKCNGDM0",
    "question": "How long was the longest Forsen intro?",
    "answer": "1 hour and 17 minutes",
    "hint1": null,
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "YABU",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:28.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPCPKVC8CP3AM2ECMZ6EB4",
    "question": "Fisting is?",
    "answer": "Usually 300 but it depends on the country etc",
    "hint1": null,
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "Cyclik[",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:28.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPCPPY4VAMBK3CYR9TGYQJ",
    "question": "idk kev",
    "answer": "eShrug",
    "hint1": null,
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "ur mom lol",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:28.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPCQ7H9TZMVJH7G2868ANM",
    "question": "YOU DONT REMOVE",
    "answer": "forsenE DANSGAME",
    "hint1": "f",
    "hint2": "forsenE",
    "submitter": null,
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:29.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPCQE71GKDCHYPTAC86ZCW",
    "question": "[forsen goes live]",
    "answer": "Pog LIVE",
    "hint1": null,
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": null,
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:29.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPCQHGG46ZSFT2BJT7C0PJ",
    "question": "FORSEN HAS GONE OFFLINE!",
    "answer": "FeelsGoodMan TeaTime",
    "hint1": null,
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "awezomenezz",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:29.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPCQK62NZF698H8K99ZPTG",
    "question": "What was Jan 2019 winning 5 dollar emote?",
    "answer": "forsenAYOYO",
    "hint1": "AYAYA but more Pepega",
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "Noobberry",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:29.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPCQRX467XT766QW2P5M0Z",
    "question": "Forsen‚Äôs favorite Band?",
    "answer": "The Fugees",
    "hint1": null,
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "YABU",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:29.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPCQTQQ6RX1M0XWG4JPWHJ",
    "question": "Forsen said he would call his Snus company this?",
    "answer": "If you don‚Äôt Seb‚Äôs snus you lose",
    "hint1": "Tell em chat forsenH",
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "cspice",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:29.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPCR1Y5MHHYM6CBNVPZCNG",
    "question": "Which mod has band the most people?",
    "answer": "Pajlada with 12000",
    "hint1": null,
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "owo",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:30.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPCRRQMG2XQ0DD8KXAHDDQ",
    "question": "If forsen is a high quality bagpack, who could be refered to as a lidl bagpack?",
    "answer": "hotted",
    "hint1": "PUBG tournament",
    "hint2": "He threw a smoke grenade, which infuriated andypyro.",
    "submitter": "huti",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:30.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPCS0J8GDJYDRR4WGCJHVV",
    "question": "Imagine yourself In a  situation , where you have time to type in correct 10 characters long passcode only once before the bomb detonates, what would it be? :thinking:",
    "answer": "Treehunter",
    "hint1": null,
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "Vadikus007",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:31.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPCS7KBWF4X8GT4T1G7JCG",
    "question": "What did Forsen drop 3 times during his cooking stream?",
    "answer": "The sausages ",
    "hint1": null,
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "YABU",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:31.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPCSVZZXT0AVG6D2832RN4",
    "question": "Owo admitted he cheats by reading the website to get his answers so fast?",
    "answer": "True ",
    "hint1": null,
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "Cyclik",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:32.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPCTE1B8J6CZW2SSG2V71F",
    "question": "What was Forsen's excuse for his chicken legs? ",
    "answer": "it's just a fucked up angle",
    "hint1": null,
    "hint2": "it's jus_ _ ______ __ _____",
    "submitter": "Tajmon00rvnge",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:32.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPCTV2D9K6GQ4G80GQJA20",
    "question": "*Forskin starts talking over a video without pausing it*",
    "answer": "STFU forsenSWA",
    "hint1": "_____ f________",
    "hint2": "S___ fors_____",
    "submitter": "atgazatufeelsdankman",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:33.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPCV3K7VN0QSGD6W28M052",
    "question": "What is Forsen‚Äôs favorite song?",
    "answer": "Stairway to heaven ",
    "hint1": null,
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "YABU",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:33.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPCV3VMGKT88305NH96YXK",
    "question": "Forsen found out about Juggalos while playing which game?",
    "answer": "Grand Theft Auto V",
    "hint1": null,
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "Powergo",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:33.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPCVB3FHE0DYX1RYWH67ZR",
    "question": "In Forsen's fanfic 'Eolnyss', what magical art does Gill specialise in?",
    "answer": "Explosive arts",
    "hint1": null,
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "ur mom lol",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:33.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPCVC5TR3Q4THTDJ8759CP",
    "question": "How many times did forsen die on Sonic in Boshy?",
    "answer": "4044",
    "hint1": null,
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": null,
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:33.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPCVKK6CYZVGR2G8CX3P03",
    "question": "What forsen meme is associated with an african christian man forsenE",
    "answer": "pastor lul",
    "hint1": null,
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "Snailcat ",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:33.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPCVMG13PH15RFBQR0316S",
    "question": "What is forsen's pan made out of?",
    "answer": "bronze",
    "hint1": "PagChomp",
    "hint2": "SHOW IT PagChomp",
    "submitter": "Tajmon00rvnge",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:33.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPCVVJGZKX0TP5PFA2DM5Y",
    "question": "Forsen revealed this many women watch him?",
    "answer": "47 percent",
    "hint1": null,
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "Cyclik[",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:34.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPCW6ZZ84J2X2M3TXN59X7",
    "question": "What is the most anticipated upcoming work of literature of all time?",
    "answer": "Eolnyss Chapter 4",
    "hint1": "Written by Forsen himself",
    "hint2": "_______ Chapter 4",
    "submitter": "ur mom lol",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:34.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPCWJ90EPM860EH527978C",
    "question": "In Forsen's fanfic 'Eolnyss', What move does Vincent use to defeat Bill?",
    "answer": "Dragon arts: Lance of Thunder",
    "hint1": "forsen1337 :dagger: :cloud_with_lightning:",
    "hint2": "Dragon arts: Lance of _______",
    "submitter": "ur mom lol",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:34.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPCWNATN7RQ70ES54H84DP",
    "question": "This better alternative to Nani, giggled at the destruction of the Twin Towers? ANELE",
    "answer": "Eloise",
    "hint1": null,
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": null,
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:34.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPCWNME47HBS9PT6FS48GV",
    "question": "\"I will destroy Nani's pussy tonight\" forsenE",
    "answer": "Amaz already destroyed Nani's pussy MEGALUL",
    "hint1": null,
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": null,
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:34.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPCWPT1RWED2WRKV8E9ATN",
    "question": "Which popular streamer called Forsen ‚Äòboring and repetitive‚Äô",
    "answer": "Xqcow ",
    "hint1": "Canadian",
    "hint2": "Racist",
    "submitter": "EpicMango7",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:34.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPCWQQWD871HTRSD60EM1P",
    "question": "You dumbass :/",
    "answer": "What part of Naruto Fanworks do you not understand?",
    "hint1": "What part of ______ ________ __ ___ ___ __________?",
    "hint2": "What part of Naruto Fanworks do ___ ___ __________?",
    "submitter": "ur mom lol",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:35.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPCXBG0T3Y795WDJ5TRDED",
    "question": "In Forsen's fanfic 'Eolnyss', Gill uses this ability to knock Molly unconscious. ",
    "answer": "Explosive arts: Release",
    "hint1": null,
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "ur mom lol",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:35.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPCXVPTEZKCCDJCMNZB40B",
    "question": "In chapter 3 of the fanfic 'Eolnyss' who are the two Rebels the protagonists fight?",
    "answer": "Gill and Bill",
    "hint1": null,
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "ur mom lol",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:36.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPCY7GE57P11PKDGP8FPD6",
    "question": "honestly __________ reminds me alot of myself and I'm happy he made something of his life. it inspires me",
    "answer": "Greekgodx",
    "hint1": null,
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "Shadowcrimson",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:36.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPCYAXQ3ARDG53G1EJMFCH",
    "question": "Which game did Forsen play?",
    "answer": "Devil May Cry 5",
    "hint1": null,
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "Cyclik[",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:36.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPCYPMPCRY2DSC54SCZED5",
    "question": "Do we need more Xqcow questions?",
    "answer": "Yes of course",
    "hint1": null,
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "GolanTrev",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:37.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPCYSH94K2EKZDRYR26Z7M",
    "question": "What is the best emote ever that should be readded??",
    "answer": "forsenOG",
    "hint1": "Swagtank",
    "hint2": "He wears the best shades",
    "submitter": null,
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:37.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPCYZA57EGBYDDSABPCN87",
    "question": "Mods...",
    "answer": "ban Vadikus and samme1g",
    "hint1": null,
    "hint2": "Permaban them.",
    "submitter": "Tajmon00rvnge",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:37.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPCZAWTBCJEKZ2695QE186",
    "question": "What is Forsen‚Äôs favorite game?",
    "answer": "Half life 2",
    "hint1": null,
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "YABU",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:37.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPCZBR6MZW2PGYQDZHDVJF",
    "question": "How old was Forsen when he met Nina?",
    "answer": "25",
    "hint1": "Twenty",
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "EpicMango7",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:37.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPCZGGRAATCJ4C6P1E8GR7",
    "question": "Title of forsen's most viewed video on Youtube by 2018?",
    "answer": "Forsen laughing to Death",
    "hint1": null,
    "hint2": "ForsenE forsenHead  ‚ö∞Ô∏è ",
    "submitter": "atgazatufeelsdankman",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:37.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPCZT4S4MN9K951RSEH4RM",
    "question": "What Snus does Forskin use the most?",
    "answer": "General XR",
    "hint1": null,
    "hint2": "G___________ ___",
    "submitter": "atgazatufeelsdankman",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:38.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPCZTRSPYF9PTWHKXMFFP5",
    "question": "A good password for your Server?",
    "answer": "treehunter",
    "hint1": null,
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": null,
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:38.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPCZVB7XCJCP841MC7CE9X",
    "question": "I voted for?",
    "answer": "forsen",
    "hint1": "EleGiggle",
    "hint2": "Not reynad",
    "submitter": "SELLOUTSEN",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:38.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPD00MENN2V295QBW1C8E8",
    "question": "What is Forsen's death count for Sonic in 'I Wanna Be the Boshy?'",
    "answer": "4044",
    "hint1": null,
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "chiaryan",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:38.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPD0RRD9Q68MBA0E11SNMN",
    "question": "How many fan of knives cards did Forsen get?",
    "answer": "Four",
    "hint1": "forsenE",
    "hint2": "for senE",
    "submitter": "Tajmon00rvnge",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:39.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPD13E2ZBS2KNCX84893JY",
    "question": "EVERY SINGEL ONE",
    "answer": "forsenC forsenGun",
    "hint1": "(Plebs)",
    "hint2": "forsen_ ___________",
    "submitter": "atgazatufeelsdankman",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:39.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPD1DY92THR6DA5XQG8N9S",
    "question": "Emote of forsen making the nazi salute.",
    "answer": "forsenHiYo",
    "hint1": "Not to be confused with a cute weeb emote.",
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "huti",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:39.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPD1G2DVMD8K8V0KTKW2J0",
    "question": "You are allowed this number of NaM s per message",
    "answer": "Two",
    "hint1": "it's more than one OMGScoods",
    "hint2": "it's less than three OMGScoods",
    "submitter": "ur mom lol",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:39.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GEFPD1MDG32SGGX9VF8ZGMH6",
    "question": "How gay is Forsen?",
    "answer": "30%",
    "hint1": null,
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "rsdidd",
    "createdAt": "2022-10-03T19:50:40.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GQSX9NDTN9BMVMZS7K7S33R5",
    "question": "How is \"Notch apple\" called in the Forsen's Language Pack?",
    "answer": "Legendary Cosmetic Apple",
    "hint1": "cosmetic LULE",
    "hint2": "PogChamp WAAAAAAAH",
    "submitter": "zneix",
    "createdAt": "2023-01-27T15:24:49.000Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "01GQSXC273G9WPAAJJ5DZEENQG",
    "question": "When will forsen beat xqc?",
    "answer": "today",
    "hint1": "forsenSmug SmugTime",
    "hint2": null,
    "submitter": "zneix",
    "createdAt": "2023-01-27T15:26:08.000Z"
  }
]
